18号
Number 18.
Baltimore Orioles棒球队球员
Conine
Conine.
我也知道
I knew that one.
好了 这个让Mikey猜
All right, this one's for Mikey.
- 您需要点什么? - 嗯 请给我来一杯柠檬汁
- Can I help you? - Yeah, one lemonade, please.
准备好了吗?
You ready?
6号
Number 6.
我知道
I know it.
Sean 嘘
Sean, shush.
David Segui?
是Melvin Mora 呆瓜
Melvin Mora, numbnuts.
我以为Mora是9号
I thought Mora was number 9.
小伙子们 我们来玩间谍游戏吧 还记得怎么玩吗
Guys, we're gonna play that spy game. Remember the spy game?
- 嗯 - 跟踪谁
- Yeah. - Who's it?
那边那个高个黑人
That tall black guy over there.
你应该说非裔美国人 爸爸
You're supposed to say African-American, Dad.
嗯 是非裔美国人
African-American, then.
- 我在前你在后 - 上次我就在后面
- I'm the front, you're the follow. - I was the follow last time.
别吵了 去吧 快去
Don't argue, go on. Go.
快啊!
Come on!
交给我吧
I got him.
对 他们都是棕色头发 一个这么高 另一个大概这么高...
Yeah, they're both brown hair, one that big, the other about that big...
他穿着...我不知道他它妈的穿了什么 他....
And he's wearing, I don't know what the fuck he's wearing. He's....
请Michael和Sean McNulty 到商场后部的办公室报到
Will Michael and Sean McNulty please report to the offices at the rear of the market.
Michael和Sean McNulty
Michael and Sean McNulty.
请速来报到
Please report.
火线重案组 第一季 第八集 功课
The Wire S01E08 Lessons
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"你要敢动王 那就千万别失手"  -- Omar
一个公用电话停用 不能说明什么
One pay phone goes down, don't mean shit.
两个同时停用 就有鬼了
Both at the same time, that's a plan.
我们打草惊蛇了
We spooked them.
抓捕那个送货的?
Busting the runner?
可能是因为这个 可能是别的
Maybe it's that, maybe it's something else.
我们还掌控高楼区的电话
We still got the tower phones.
目前我们也在监控Stringer Bell的寻呼机
And we're up on Stringer Bell's pager now, too.
是 但这说明了这些家伙是多么谨慎
Yeah, but this shows just how cautious these guys are.
我们稍有行动 他们就会改变策略
We make any play, and they're ready to change up on us.
如果他们不用平房区的公用电话...
If they're not using the pay phones in the low-rises...
那他们怎么办?
Then what are they doing?
他们去另一个公用电话亭
They're walking to another pay phone.
我们也许会发现高楼区的公用电话使用率上升
We might see more traffic on the tower pay phones.
明天有警员测试 对吧
Sergeants' test's tomorrow, right?
下午四点
4:00 in the afternoon.
这次你不参加吗
You ain't gonna take it this time?
参加 为什么不参加
Sure, why not?
你不学习吗
You ain't gonna study?
我会的
Sure I am.
你们得跟踪Pit里的一些混混...
You guys need to follow some of the boys out of the Pit...
看他们用什么取代公用电话
And see what they're using for pay phones.
对不起 这是个直接的命令吗
Excuse me, is that a direct order?
我只是说...
I'm just saying--
如果你想跟踪那些混蛋 从一个电话亭到另一个电话...
If you wanna follow these assholes from phone to phone...
你干嘛不自己去
Why don't you do it yourself?
我做文案工作 记得吗
I'm in-office, remember?
- 对了 他们拿走了你的枪 - 因为你向自己的车射击
- Right, they took your gun. - For shooting your car.
不 那是上一次
No, that was before.
- 没错 这次是别的什么事 - 对
- That's right, that was something else. - Right.
你能相信吗
You believe this guy?
好像他算老几似的
Like there are fucking stripes on his sleeve.
你们今天得上屋顶
You guys need to get up on those rooftops today.
去看看那些混混用什么替代了电话
See what these mopes are using for phones.
过来 瞧这鸟玩意儿
Come here, look at this shit.
啥鸟东西
What the fuck is that?
- 我瞅瞅 - Bird告诉过我这鸟事
- Let me look at that shit. - Bird told me that shit.
瞧呀 瞧呀
Look at that.Look at that.
操他妈的兔子 去他妈的
Fucking peter-puffer, get the fuck out of here.
Omar先生 你要这个针头吗
Mr. Omar, you want ends on this?
不 亲爱的 我挺好
No, darling, I'm cool.
衬衫不错
Nice shirt.
呵 去你的
Yeah, fuck you.
在Baltimore警局凶杀科 穿粉红衬衫是需要勇气的
It takes guts wearing a pink shirt on the BPD Homicide unit.
是的 没错
Yes, it does.
要么有勇气 要么熟悉非主流生活方式
Guts, or a familiarity with alternative lifestyles.
- 你在追查什么 - 丰田佳美
- What are you chasing? - Toyota Camry.
谁的车
Whose?
登记在一个住县郊的女人名下...
It's listed to some woman with a county address...
但周六 我调查的Stringer Bell在用这辆车
But Saturday, my man Stringer Bell was using it.
你周末值班?
You were working the weekend?
不 我和孩子们在东北区商场 好吧
No, I'm down in the Northeast market with the kids, right?
- 猜谁出现在我面前 - String那天也血拼咯?
- Who should appear before me? - Market day for String, too?
我知道如果我太靠近他会认出我来
I know he makes me if I get too close,
于是我让Sean和Michael一前一后跟着他
so I tell Sean and Michael front-and-follow.
他们太厉害了 我都跟丢了 吓掉了魂
They're so good, I lose track of them, scared the shit out of myself.
但他们跟得紧紧的 发现佳美车...
But they stay with him, spec the Camry...
然后Sean 我的亲骨肉 记下了车牌号
And Sean, my flesh and blood, gets the tag.
你孩子懂得前后包夹?
Your kids know front-and-follow?
他们可中意这玩意儿了 有时候我们在购物中心玩间谍游戏
They fucking love it. We play spy in the mall sometimes.
反正我拿到了一个 住在Woodmore的女人的地址...
Anyhow, I got a Woodmore address of a woman...
她借车给Stringer Bell
Who lends her wheels to Stringer Bell.
- 这是个突破口 - 瞧这McNulty一家 老天
- It's a start. - The fucking family McNulty. Jesus.
咋了
What?
Wallace
Wallace.
嘿 Wallace
Yo, Wallace.
- 啥事 - 嘿 Wallace
- What? - Yo, Wallace.
- 啥事 - 这个啥意思啊
- What? - What's this about here?
是这个吗?
This one here?
"一辆在中央大道行驶的巴士在出发站上来8位乘客"
"A bus traveling on Central Avenue begins its route by picking up eight passengers.
"接着 又上来4位 然后又有2位 下去1位"
"Next, it picks up four more, and then an additional two, while discharging one.
"在倒数第二站 3位乘客下了车..."
"At the next-to-last stop, three passengers get off the bus...
- "又上来2位" - 嘿Wallace
- "and another two get on. " - Hey, Wallace.
"到终点站车上有多少位乘客?"
How many passengers are on the bus at the last stop?"
心算嘛
Just do it in your head.
嘿 今天有试用品来
Yo, testers coming out today.
新包装
New package.
等下我可能会过去
I might be down later.
等下?
Later?
听着 等下我去找你 行吗
Look, I'll catch you around the way, all right?
Wallace 哥们 你不能就躺在这儿啊
Wallace, man, you can't just lay up in here.
是7 对吗
Seven, right?
Dee一直在问
Dee been asking about shit.
- 那又怎样 - 我跟他说你病了...
- So what? - I been telling him you sick...
但你知道纸是包不住火的
But you know he won't let me carry that too much longer.
听着 我等一会儿过去
Now, look, I be down later sometime.
- 不行 哥们 试用品马上就来了 - 听着 哥们 去他的试用品 行吗
- No, man, testers gonna be out. - Look, man, fuck the testers, all right?
去它的试用品 去它的Dee 它妈的都去见鬼
Fuck the testers, fuck Dee, fuck all that shit.
给我10美元 周五前还你
Just let me hold $10, and I'll give it back to you by Friday.
怎么还 你不工作Dee不会付你工资
How? Dee ain't gonna pay you for not working.
听着 你要不要给我10美元?
Look, you gonna let me hold $10, or not?
是8吗
Eight?
该死 Sarah 听着 闭上眼
Damn, Sarah, look. Close your eyes.
你在场地上贩毒 20支长粉瓶
You working a ground stash. 20 tall pinks.
两个瘾君子过来各自要了两支 又来一个要了三支
Two fiends come up and ask for two each, another one cops three.
然后Bodie又给你10支 然后一个白人开车过来...
Then Bodie hands you 10 more, but a white guy rolls up in a car...
拦下你 买了8支
Waves you down, and pays for eight.
你还剩几支?
How many vials you got left?
15支
Fifteen.
你这都能算对 它妈的书上的题目怎么就做不来呢
How the fuck can you keep the count right, but not do the book problem?
如果算错了 他们会扁你
Count be wrong, they'll fuck you up.
- 不 他去找你 - 今天吗
- No, he coming to you. - Today?
- 是的 - 他很急吗
- Yeah. - He in a rush or something?
不 是我们要求的
No, we told him to do it like that.
他昨晚向我们伸手要 所以我们就让他今天一早就过去找你
He had his hand out last night and we told him first thing today.
- 他会进楼吗? - 不 不会
- He ain't coming into the tower? - No, not like that.
给他20 他不会逗留 明白吗
Just run 20 on down to him. He gonna roll on his way, all right?
- 大概一小时后到吧 - 谁认识他?
- Be there in, like, an hour, maybe. - Who gonna know?
- Little Man 他认识Day - 好的
- Little Man, he know Day. - All right.
那是Stringer Bell吗
That was Stringer Bell?
在15分钟前收到一个寻呼后 打给高楼区1号公用电话
Calling tower pay phone number 1, after taking a page 15 minutes ago.
- 我们认识 Little Man吗 - 是的
- We know Little Man? - Yeah.
221大楼的头儿
Enforcer in the 221 building.
好了 那么他大概在半小时后 从221大楼里出来...
Okay, so he's rolling out of the 221 in about a half an hour or so...
带着20个什么货 交给一个叫Day的人
With 20 whatevers to hand off to someone named Day.
货从高楼区送出来
Product coming out of the towers.
通常我们都是盯着送进去的
We're usually trying to catch it going in.
嗯 如果想抓到他们 我们就得抓紧啦
Yeah, if you wanna catch them, we're gonna have to hustle.
Wallace 哥们 他可烦人了
Wallace, man, he bugging.
- 他在哪儿 - 哪儿也没去
- Where he be at? - Nowhere.
他一天到晚都躺在床上 知道吗
He just lays around all day, you know?
苦苦哀求我给他买三明治的钱
Begged my ass off for sandwich money.
你担心他吗
You worried about him?
我是说 那小子不大对劲 Dee
I mean, shit ain't right, Dee.
你可能什么时候得和他谈谈
You might consult with him some.
搞什么鬼 哥们 如果他不想过来 那是他的事
What the fuck, man? lf he don't wanna be down here, that's on him.
我是说 又没人拿枪指着他的头什么的
I mean, ain't like nobody holding no gun to his head or nothing.
嗯 但他成天无所事事
Yeah, but he ain't about nothing else.
他整天整夜呆在在房间里
He up in his room and shit, all the damn day.
好吧 叫Wallace来见我
All right, tell Wallace to come see me.
好的
All right.
我过去一下
Be right back.
已经2小时了
It's been two hours.
要是Little Man今天不在221大楼上班怎么办
What if Little Man ain't working in the 221 today?
要是这个叫Day的人不来怎么办
What if this Day guy don't come?
要是他来了 我们错过了接头怎么办
What if he came, and we missed the pick-up?
嘿 Herc 要是你爸妈从没见过面怎么办
Yo, Herc, what if your mother and father never met?
- 生意如何 - 蒸蒸日上
- How's shop doing? - Steady rolling.
行 来兜个风吧
All right, let's take a ride.
- 饕餮去 - 饕餮去 上哪儿
- Beef run. - Beef run, where at?
Pulaski 宝贝 好地方
Pulaski, baby, the good shit.
上车吧 哥们
Get in the car, man.
嘿 Poot 接下来一小时你管事
Yo, Poot. You the man for an hour.
它妈的 看我多牛
Shit, look at me.
- Kima - 林肯车 我们盯上了
- Kima. - The Lincoln, we're on it.
别急
Hang back.
看看他上哪儿去
Let's see where he goes.
我不明白 一直不明白
I don't understand that, never did.
该死的Bey 那么多辣妞你怎么能坐怀不乱呢
Damn, Bey, how can you stand that shit with all that hot shit on it?
哥们 技巧在于别去在意 我有这能力 你知道我的
Man, trick is not to give a fuck, boy. I got this, you know me.
什么状况啊 我叔叔今天放你们的假吗
So what? My uncle's cut y'all loose today?
不 我们在庆祝
No, we're celebrating.
Stinkum在新地盘赚到了提成
Stinkum got some points for some fresh territory.
我听说了 你们提成多少?
I heard about that. How much is yours in the package?
20%
20.
我们要去灭了那里的地头蛇
We gotta run off the niggers that been down there.
没什么大不了 不过是群不入流的混混
Ain't no thing. Bunch of off-brand niggers is all.
你一如既往地经营Pit 你也会得到提成的
You keep running that pit the way you been, you gonna see points, too.
嗯 他妈的 我等着这一天呢
Yeah, you know, shit, I'm here waiting.
这一天会来的 是吧 Stink?
It'll come, right, Stink?
嗯 我和Orlando聊过
Yeah, I been talking to Orlando, right?
他说他在新奥尔良有优质可卡因的货源
He said he got this good coke connect from New Orleans.
Orlando?
他想让我在庭院里卖他的私货 私底下给我些好处
He want me to put what he can get out into the court, a little extra on the side.
我不清楚 Dee 你最好和你舅舅谈谈
I don't know, Dee, you better talk to your uncle about that.
- 是的 没错 - 听到了吗
- Yeah, definitely. - Hear that?
嗯 我会听听他怎么说 嗯
Yeah, I'm gonna see what he say on it. Yeah.
但是 今天是你的日子 哥们
But, you know, today is your day, man.
- Stink日 - 也是他的夜晚
- Stink day. - His night, too.
是啊 哥们 今晚我们要耍一把 老爹
Yeah, man, we gonna break out tonight, daddy.
用Little Man的车 带一些Orlando的靓妞过去吧
Bring some of Orlando's good pussy over there by Little Man's.
- 好 - 好
-Yeah. -Yeah.
你去吗 去吗
You up there? You up?
- 嗨 他去 - 你去
- Yeah, he up. - You up.
小子 我去! 你不必问两遍
Nigger, I'm up! You don't gotta ask twice.
- 咋了 - 不准喝
- What's wrong? - No.
他现在在意了
He give a fuck now.
水
Water.
- 从车里出来 先生 - 我做了什么
- Step out of the car, sir. - What did I do?
从车里出来
Step out of the car.
到我搭档那儿去 去吧
Go around to my partner, here.
哥们 听着 我已经迟到了
Man, look, I'm already late.
请把双手放到车顶 先生
Put your hands on the roof, please, sir.
先生 在市内一指定 禁毒禁止游荡区域有人看到...
Sir, you were observed in one of the city's designated drug-free, anti-loitering zones...
一毒贩嫌疑人探进你车里 递给你什么东西
Where a drug suspect leaned into your vehicle handing you something.
并且当我们示意你停车...
And when we signaled for you to stop...
你弯下腰去 似乎把什么藏匿 在乘客座位的下方
You leaned over as if concealing something beneath the passenger seat.
听着 够了
Look, enough of this shit, now.
先生 座位底下有藏什么东西吗
Is there something beneath that seat, sir?
没有
No.
那么你不会介意我们看一眼 对吧
Then you don't mind if we look, right?
去你们的 真是鬼话连篇
Fuck y'all. This is some bullshit.
这个你们管不着 好吧?
That's none of your business, all right?
我就要管 怎么着
How about if I make it my business?
你呼我?
You rang?
- 他是谁 - Damien Lavell Price
- Who's he? - Damien Lavell Price.
他从221大楼里拿了2万美元
He takes $20,000 in cash out of the 221 building.
Lester从一部高楼区电话里窃听到这次接头
Lester picked up the drop from one of the tower phones.
我们跟踪他到Hill水库直到他发现我们
We followed him up Reservoir Hill till he spotted us.
他是个立委侍从?
He's a legislative aide?
谁呼我
Who paged me?
他在你办公室
He's in your office.
我们逮着他带着2万美元现金
We popped him with $20,000 in cash.
- 有什么样的合理依据 - 监听电话得来
- What kind of PC? - Right off the wire.
在高楼区的一个电话机上 Stringer Bell和某人通话
Stringer Bell to someone on a tower phone.
我们以为会查获毒品
We thought we were gonna come up with drugs.
结果是钱
Got money instead.
我认识这个人
I know this guy.
Orioles队(巴尔的摩棒球队)昨晚赢了
Orioles won last night.
候补队员英勇对抗波士顿队
Bullpen stood up to Boston.
那些钱是你打劫换来的?
You get that money cracking cribs, or what?
我要和我的律师说话
I'd like to speak to my attorney.
他在我去的那个资金筹集会上 为一名政客开车
He was driving for a politician at this fundraiser I went to.
- 哪个政客? - 来自Annapolis的某个...
- Which one? - Someone from Annapolis...
至少从他的身份证上看是这样
From the looks of his ID, anyway.
我们要指控他什么罪名
What do we charge here?
他说钱是他的吗
He say the money's his?
他屁都没放一个
He doesn't say shit.
扣下现金 给他写张收据
Keep the cash, write him a receipt.
他想向市律师索回 可以
He wants to put a claim in to the city solicitor, he can.
但他们会问他钱是从哪儿得到的
But they're gonna ask him where he got the pile.
死亡天使
The angel of death.
那是谁
Who's that?
Reed警长 内务部
Major Reed, lID.
中尉 我有话对你说
Lieutenant, a word.
你好吗
What's up?
过得怎样?
How you doing?
我?
Me?
是啊 你 一切都好吗
Yeah, you. Everything is good?
还不错
I'm all right.
我是说 你缺钱花吗 哥们?
I mean, you fixed for cash or something, man?
因为如果你缺点什么...
'Cause if you need a little something...
真的 你要做的 是只管张口要
Really, the thing to do is just to ask for it.
我所做的一切 不过是往你口袋里塞钱...
That's all I do, is put money in your pocket...
确保你他妈的不会忘本!
And make sure you don't stray from the nest!
坐下
Sit down.
听着 我他妈的最不愿看到的
Listen, the last motherfucking thing I need
就是我卖酒执照的清白名声
is for the clean name on my liquor license...
他妈的被你玷污 你明白吧
To be dirtied the fuck up by you. You understand that?
Avon 好了 哥们 好了 Avon
Avon, come on, man. Avon.
它妈的本分点!
Do your fucking job!
我向州人事部核实过了
I checked with the state Personnel Department.
他在Davis参议员行政区办公室工作
He's on the payroll of Senator Davis' district office...
已经一年多了
For more than a year.
他因为日间入室抢劫 在Hagerstown坐了四年牢
He did four years in Hagerstown for daytime B and E.
之前还有多项毒品指控和 一项醉酒驾驶指控
Before that, drug charges and a PBJ on a check charge.
现在我们逮着他从高楼区出来
And now we catch him coming out of the towers...
带着整齐地扎成捆的2万美金
With $20,000 in manicured, banded money.
你以什么罪名把他抓进来
You brought him in here on what charge?
以追缴犯罪所得为目的的刑事措施
民事财产没收
Civil forfeiture.
在他告诉我们那些钱的合法来源之前 由我们保管
Until he tells us a legitimate source for that money, we keep it.
那么你没有刑事指控?
So you have no criminal charge.
没有 只有钱
No, just the money.
还回去
Give it back.
- 长官? - 把钱还给那个人
- Sir? - Give the man back his money.
长官 我们监听到
Sir, we pulled this off the wire...
一个嫌疑犯让另一个人准备好接头
With one of our suspects telling another to expect a pick-up.
车里是毒品的钱
It's drug money in that car.
把钱还给他
Give him back his money.
报告写成无根据拦车
Write it up as an unwarranted car stop.
我要求你给一个毒贩子立一项罪名 中尉
Now I ask you to put a charge on a drug dealer, Lieutenant.
仅此而已
That's all I ask.
现在搭线窃听 克隆寻呼机 宣誓书搅得我不得安生
And now I got wiretaps, pager clones, affidavits coming out of my ass.
而且你还狗拿耗子 多管闲事
And you're in people's shit where you're not supposed to be.
- 长官 - 我结束这些破事 副队
- Sir-- - I'm shutting this down, Lieutenant.
有什么罪名立什么罪名 周末之前弄好
You charge what you can, and you do it by the end of the week.
- 我们没做错事 - 你抓了一个立委侍从
- We did nothing wrong here. - You jacked up a senatorial aide.
你从他口袋里掏出2万美金
You went into his pocket, pulled out $20,000.
尽管没有刑事指控 你认为扣下钱是明智之举
And though there's no criminal charge, you think it wise to try to keep it.
你不仅给自己丢脸...
You shit all over yourself...
还给我 给局里丢脸
All over me, all over this department.
我告诉过你 别给我什么"惊喜" 记得吗
Now, I told you, no surprises, remember?
2万 正好
$20,000, even.
在这儿签字 或者你需要的话可以自己数数看
Sign here, or you can count it yourself, if you want.
那么我可以走了吗
So I can leave now?
有谁能告诉我 它妈的这是怎么回事
Will somebody please tell me what the fuck that was about?
真荒唐
This is bullshit.
我们刚刚送还2万块Barksdale的钱
We just gave back 20 large of Barksdale's money.
嘿 它妈的怎么回事
Hey, what the fuck?
我猜猜 是副局?
Let me guess, the Deputy?
他怎么会这么快就掺和进来
How's he got onto this so quick?
- 我告诉他的 - 你告诉他的?
- I told him. - You told him?
你干嘛要告诉他
Why would you be telling him?
他是执行副局 我逮捕了一名州议员侍从
He's the Deputy for Operations, I arrested an aide to a state senator.
我怎么能不告诉他
How do I not tell him?
你有没有注意到参议员没有哼一声
Have you noticed there hasn't been a complaint from the senator?
知道为什么吗
Know why?
他的司机为何从高楼区带这么多钱出来
What is his driver doing coming out of the high-rises with so much money?
- 我和副局说了 - 他怎么说
- I told the Deputy that. - What did he say?
不要多管闲事?
Mind our own business?
把钱还给那个人 然后一边凉快去?
Give the man back his money and go the fuck away?
差不多
Pretty much.
而且他还说了一些为我着想的话
Except he said a few things for my benefit, too.
比如我怎样给他丢脸
Like how I had shit all over him.
比如这周他要结束我们的行动
Like how he was shutting us down this week.
- 结束个鸟 - 我们没戏了
- The fuck he is. - We're done.
过了周五 我就被雪藏 他和我说了
I go past Friday, and I'm buried. He told me that.
他要雪藏你? 凭什么 你只是它妈的尽你的职责
He's gonna bury you? For what? You're doing your fucking job.
你以为只要尽职我就没事了? 你就没事了?
You think the job is gonna save me? You think it's gonna save you?
指挥链 这就是今天我从副局那儿学到的
Chain-of-command. That's all I got from the Deputy, today.
指挥链?
Chain-of-command?
你有告诉警长参议员司机的事吗 或者上校?
Did you tell your major about the senator's driver? Or the Colonel?
没有? 那还谈什么指挥链?
No? Then where's your chain-of-command?
凭什么一个中尉直接走后门 越级上报给执行副局?
What's the shift lieutenant doing going up the back stairs to the Deputy Ops?
- 你在说什么 - 没什么
- What are you saying? - Nothing.
它妈的没错
Goddamn right.
怎么 是他有什么你的把柄吗?
Why, he got something on you?
你说你副局能听你的 他它妈的抓着你什么把柄了?
You say you got the Deputy's ear. What the fuck's he got on you?
只是警衔不同 警探
Only rank, Detective.
嘿 Stink 忘了规矩了?
Yo, Stink. What about the rules, yo?
特殊情况嘛
Special occasion, yo.
嘿 Bey
Yo, Bey.
- 我要吐了 - 不 你不会吐的
- I'm gonna throw up. - No, you ain't.
Burrell认为我冒犯了他
Burrell thinks I crossed him.
他和你这样说了?
He said this to you?
说了一大通
In so many words.
- 那你该辩解 - 辩解什么
- You need to explain then-- - Explain what?
我接了一个无底洞一样的案子?
That I'm bringing in a case that goes everywhere?
今天是某个参议员的司机
Today, it was some senator's driver.
两天后可能就是市议会议员了
Two days from now, a city councilman, maybe.
他要求给Barksdale指控一项罪名 仅此而已
He asked for a charge on Barksdale. That's all he asked for.
这个立委侍从的事 谁能预见到呢
This thing with the legislative aide, who could've foreseen it?
他预见到了
He saw it.
Burrell
Burrell.
看 这就是公开的秘密
See, this is the thing that everyone knows and no one says.
你追踪毒品 就能立毒品案
You follow the drugs, you get a drug case.
你一追踪钱 就找不着北了
You start following the money, you don't know where you're going.
这就是为什么他们不想要搭线窃听或线上克隆
That's why they don't want wiretaps or wired Cls
或其他他们无法掌控的东西
or anything they can't control.
因为一旦窃听开始 谁知道会说些什么呢
Because once that tape starts rolling, who the hell knows what's going to be said?
那个狗娘养的McNulty 还问我副局抓到我什么把柄
That son of a bitch McNulty asked me what the Deputy had on me.
他真的问了我
He actually asked me that.
你怎么说
What did you say?
人都到哪去了 那些妞呢
Where everybody go? Where the girls go?
操 哥们 派对散了
Fuck it, man, party broke.
我们喝完了 操完了
We drunked out and fucked out.
你们都让我去买酒 我还没回来 派对就完了?
You all send me out for liquor, and by the time I get back, the shit is dead?
看这个
Look at this.
尼克斯队(NBA球队)又搞砸了自己的球员选秀
The Knicks done fucked up their draft again.
嘿 她怎么了
What's with her?
哦 把她操晕过去了 我能说啥呢
Oh, fucked her silly. What can I say?
她还吸掉了一半我们带来的货 那个贪婪的骚货
She snorted half the shit we brought up in here, too, that greedy bitch.
嘿 Bey
Yo, Bey.
- 您想见我们 - 这是怎么回事
- You wanted to see us? - What the hell is this?
我今早收到的
I got copied this morning.
正如上面写的一样
It's just what it looks like.
执行副局Rawls和Forester签过字的备忘录 让我们收拾东西
A memo signed by the Deputy Ops, Rawls and Forester, telling us to pack it in.
周五之前停止窃听 周一前把电脑运送到药管局
We come down on the wire by Friday, ship the computers to the DEA by Monday...
下周末前能指控几个就指控几个
And charge whoever we have by the end of next week.
是吗 都搞定谁了
Yeah? Who do you have?
一些二流角色 Anton Artis 又名Stinkum
Couple of mid-level guys. Anton Artis, a.k.a. Stinkum.
名叫Bird的枪手 因谋杀Gant被通缉
Shooter named Bird, wanted for killing Gant.
就是你庭审时的目击证人
He was the witness in your court.
就这些?
That's it?
是的 外加一些小喽啰
Except for a couple of hangers-on, yeah.
他们为什么这么做
Why are they doing this?
为什么选这个时候
Why now?
昨天我们逮着一个 拿着袋子从高楼区出来的人
We picked up a bag man coming out of the high-rises...
带着2万美元现金
Carrying $20,000 in cash, yesterday.
那又如何
So?
他为Clay Davis做事
So, he works for Clay Davis.
39号行政区
Of the 39th Legislative District.
副局很生气
The deputy was displeased.
不过没事了
It's okay, though.
我们还了钱 道了歉
We gave the money back, said we were sorry.
- Daniels能怎么办 - 凉拌
- What can Daniels do? - Not a fucking thing.
副局给了他直接的命令 和你桌上这一份一样
The Deputy sent him the same direct order you have on your desk right there.
给我接通Burrell!
Get me Burrell on the line!
警探们 当你们发誓你们会全力以赴
Detectives, when you swore that your affidavit was true...
遵守宣誓书的条约
To the best of your ability,
Baltimore的巡回法庭如何反应
What did the Circuit Court of Baltimore do?
- 您给了我们窃听的权力 - 期限多久 McNulty警探?
- You gave us the wire. - For how long, Detective McNulty?
60天 不是吗?
Sixty days, no?
而你们监控这些电话有多久
And how long have you monitored these phone extensions?
大概40天吧
Forty days, maybe.
Burrell副局已经接通
Deputy Burrell is on the line.
Erv 我是Phelan
Erv, it's Phelan.
老兄 你在耍我吧
Kiddo, you're fucking with me here.
是的 你就是
Yes, you are.
Erv 听我说
Erv, listen to me.
巡回法庭签订两个命令
The Circuit Court signed two orders...
批准共60天的电话监控
For a total of 60 days of telephonic surveillance.
现在我正看着一份你办公室发来的备忘录
Now, I'm looking at a copy of a memo from your office...
告诉我没有60天了
Telling me I can't have my 60 days.
你根本不在听
You're not hearing me.
Baltimore巡回法庭命令监听60天
The Circuit Court for Baltimore ordered 60 days on this tap.
法庭要求60天
The Court wants its 60 days.
如果你周五撤下监听行动 那你周一就会被指控藐视法庭
Now, if you take this wire down on Friday, you'll be in contempt of court on Monday.
明白?
Understood?
向Arlene和孩子们问好
And all the best to Arlene and the kids.
好的
Yeah.
现在谁是你老子
Who's your daddy now?
听着 我啥也没干 副队 上面向你发牢骚 都是法官惹的祸
Look, I didn't do a damn thing, Lieutenant. You got a beef, it's with the judge.
是的 他收到副局的备忘录 他自己走了一招棋
Yeah, he got the Deputy's memo, he called his own shot.
如果你不相信我就问Greggs吧
Ask Greggs if you don't believe me.
听着 我要挂了
Look, I've got to go.
Kima
Kima.
副局来电 火冒三丈
Deputy called, mad as the devil.
叫他们别收拾了 我们继续监听
Tell them to quit packing. We're back up on the wire.
Kima
Kima.
McNulty还是法官? 还是两者都是?
McNulty or the judge? Or both?
这一次是法官
This time, the judge.
考我一个问题 任何问题
Ask me a question. Any question.
我以为你没学习呢
I thought you weren't studying.
这工作是常识 考我个问题吧 瘪三
This job is common sense. Ask me a question, dickless.
看我掌握得如何
See how I do.
"根据Q1--"
"According to Q1--"
等等 告诉我
Hold up, help me out, here.
你得知道它们的序号吗?
You have to know them by the numbers?
这样有好处嘛
It helps.
这样听上去更专业
Makes it sound more professional that way.
"根据Q1 ..."
"According to Q1 ...
"性骚扰的一般法规"
"the general order covering sexual harassment...
"当一位你小队的女警官抱怨"
"in the event a female officer in your squad complains...
"她的搭档对她进行性骚扰时"
"that her side partner has sexually harassed her...
"你应该:"
"you should:
"A: 报告指挥官"
"A: Notify the commanding officer.
"B: 报告副队长"
"B: Notify the shift lieutenant.
"C: 报告最高级女警官"
"C: Notify the ranking female officer."
我选D
I go with D.
D?
嗯 敢碰我的妞儿 耳光扇死他
Yeah, bitch-slap the side partner for dipping into my private stock...
然后带妞回家 一直操她到花容尽放
Then take missy home and fuck her till she smiles.
巴尔的摩市社区大学
搞什么?
What the hell?
当价格的微小变动引起需求的巨大变化时
When a small change in price creates a large change in demand...
这种需求被称作弹性需求 但有些产品是无弹性的
Then demand is said to be elastic, but some products are inelastic.
就是说 价格的变动不会影响需求
Meaning, a change in price does not affect demand.
什么是影响需求弹性的关键因素
Some key factors that affect the elasticity of demand are what?
- Bell先生? - 欲望
- Mr. Bell? - Desire.
消费需要
Consumer need.
没错 确切地说就是消费者推迟购买的能力
Right, specifically, the ability of a consumer to delay acquisition.
宏观经济学导论
还有什么因素影响弹性？
What else can affect the elasticity?
我铅笔芯断了
My pencil lost its point.
娘们都这么说
All the girls say so.
Damon 我们接到了订单 工作却一点都没进展
Damon, we got work orders here, and ain't nothing happening.
这些活昨天就到期了 人们会进来索要成品
These jobs were due yesterday, and people going to be coming in here...
你们却什么都没干
Asking for their work and nothing been done.
哥们 去他们的 让他们等着
Man, fuck them. Let them wait.
不 你不能把街头那一套带到这里 听到了吗
No, you are not going to bring that corner bullshit up in here, you hear me?
你们知道这儿是什么情况吗
You know what we got here?
我们这个是弹性产品 知道这意味着什么吗
We got an elastic product. You know what that mean?
这意味着如果人们可以到别处去打印复印
That mean when people can go elsewhere and get their printing and copying done...
他们就会这样做
They gonna do it.
你们表现得像我们有非弹性产品 但是我们没有
You acting like we got an inelastic product and we don't.
现在我要这里经营得像真正做生意的地儿
Now, I want this to run like a true fucking business.
不准有名无实 不准废话连篇
Not no front, not no bullshit.
听懂了吗
Understand me?
我是认真的
I'm serious.
你从哪儿抢来这破车
Where you snatch this old wreck from?
Frederick路那边
Out Frederick Road.
完事儿后把它丢在东区
Ditch it over Eastside when we done.
看
Check it.
他在那儿 还有另外一个傻子也在那儿
Him there, and that other fool there.
只有他们可能比较难弄
They the only ones might be trouble.
我来对付Scar 你就对付另一个操蛋的
I'll drop Scar, you just drop that other motherfucker.
不 就对付Scar 他的同伙要逃 就让他逃吧
No, just Scar. His boy break, we going to let him.
但是如果他反抗 我就搞定他 明白了吗
But if he raise up, I'm on him, see?
该死 我希望Bird也在这儿 哥们
Damn, I wish Bird was here, man.
Bird一定爱死这事儿了
Bird be loving this shit right here.
这就提醒我了 我们离开后
Which do remind me, we get up out of here...
你得把那玩意儿丢进排水沟
You need to drop that shit down a storm drain.
现在给我点时间绕过这个街区
Now give me some time to go around the block...
到另一边准备 行吗
And set up on the other side, all right?
嗨 谁有黑盖(毒品)?
What up, who got black tops?
嘿 嗨
Hey, now.
搞什么
What the fuck?
听好了 Bey
Listen here, Bey.
你要敢动王 那就千万别失手
You come at the king, you best not miss.
- Stink被放倒了 - Stink?
- Stink's been got. - Stink?
- Bey也中了一枪 在腿上 - 该死 哥们 发生了什么事
- Bey caught one, too, in the leg. - Shit, man, what happened?
他们在Edmondson街的排水沟那儿
They down the gulley on Edmondson.
该死的Scar 哥们
Fucking Scar, man.
- 不 不是他 是Omar 哥们 - Omar?
- No, it ain't him. Omar, man. - Omar?
Bounty去追踪那个贱人了
Bounty's going up on that bitch.
这可把咱们害惨了
That fucks us.
我们已经通过逮捕送货的家伙 给Stinkum立了一个罪名
We had Stinkum tied up with a bow from the arrest of the runner...
现在他这头又断了
And now he's out of the case.
这人还真我行我素
The man's a fucking loose cannon.
的确
Literally.
至少我们要训他几句
We've got to pull his ass up at least.
悬赏追杀这个基佬
There's a dime on this cocksucker's head.
你们这帮人里谁站出来
One of you motherfuckers needs to step up.
你拖着伤腿去了哪儿
Where you go with that?
Maryland综合医院
Maryland General.
我进去告诉他们 我在街角遇上了一个流浪汉
Walked up in there and told them I was on the corner, caught a stray.
- 有警察来和你谈话吗 - 就来了一辆警车 不是凶杀科
- Police come talk to you? - Just a roller, no homicide.
放出话去
Put it out there.
不仅仅是我们的人
Not just our people, either.
我说的是所有想站出来的黑鬼
I'm talking about any nigger who wants to step up.
放出话去
Put out the word.
做了Omar或任何和Omar一伙的 就赏1万美金
There's $10,000 on Omar or any motherfucker standing with Omar.
你们其他事都别干了 都给我它妈的抓人去
Y'all niggers ain't got shit to do but be on this motherfuckin' hunt.
- 行动吧 - 好的
- Now be on it. - All right.
你怎么想 哥们?
So, what you think, homes?
我在想这是整个游戏中最糟糕的部分
I'm thinking this is the worst part of the game.
最好我们能扯平了 对吧
Best we do is break out even, right?
啥
What?
我是说 这已经是个人恩怨了 没别的好处了
I'm saying, this shit got personal. Ain't nothing else to it.
那么你是说就让它过去
So, you talking about letting it slide.
也许应该暂时如此
For a time, maybe.
我是说我们放出话去 你准备停战了
I'm saying we put the word out that you ready to talk a truce.
当这个黑鬼从藏的地方冒头 你再给他致命一击
When this nigger come out from underneath his rock, you hit him.
但是目前
But right now?
事态有些失控
This shit got out of hand.
你们要我说什么
What you want me to say?
听着 Stink被放倒的事我不知道
Look, I don't know nothing about Stink getting dropped...
Bey被射伤的事我也不知道
And I don't know nothing about Bey getting shot, either.
这些疯狂的屁事我才不知道呢
I don't know about this crazy nonsense.
那不一定 消息很快就传到我们这儿
I don't know, it came back to us quick.
你们知道是怎么回事
You know how that be.
所有人都把Omar想得最坏
Everybody want to believe the worst about Omar.
可是你瞧 生者共生
But live and let live, you know?
我不认为Brandon的事你会就这么算了
I don't see you letting them slide on Brandon.
如果我要追杀某个人
If I was coming after certain people...
我决不会想让你们这些好人 有理由来"关心"我
I definitely wouldn't want to give y'all fine people any cause for concern.
这行当是有规则的 对吧
There are rules here, right?
- 规则? - 嗯
- Rules? - Yeah.
没有失误 没有目击者
No mistakes, no bystanders.
没有纳税人(普通百姓))搅进局里
No taxpayers getting caught up in the mix.
我是说 你只要走近了 攻击目标
I mean, you just get in close and you hit the right nigger.
并且事后把枪丢了 我想这也是一条规则
And lose the gun afterward, that'd be a rule, too, I think.
还有一点 Omar
One thing, Omar.
放倒Stinkum有点坏了我们的事
Having Stinkum dropped kind of fucks us on our thing.
怎么说
How so?
我们抓到Stink带着4包货去补货
We had Stink caught with 4 G-packs on a re-up.
也许我们可以在此基础上弄出点名堂
And maybe we could've built something on that.
也许可以顺藤摸瓜和Stringer一同定罪
Roll him up with Stringer, maybe.
现在他就没有把柄了
Now he's got no roll to him.
所以说 Omar Birdw的案子我们都感激你
So, the point is, Omar, while we're all grateful for the case you gave us on Bird,
并且我们欣赏你的"亲自动手"性格
And we admire your do-it-yourself nature--
我们需要你歇歇手
We need you to hang back.
听着 哥们 这不都取决于我 对吧
Look, man, it ain't all up to me, right?
我被悬赏捉拿呢
I got a bounty on my head.
嗯 我们看到那辆货车了
Yeah, we saw the van.
听着 哥们 我尽我所能帮助你们 但是游戏摆在那儿呢
Look, man, I do what I can do to help you all, but the game is out there.
要么玩 要么被玩
And it's either play or get played.
就这样吗
What, that it?
先生们 女士
Gentlemen. Ma'am.
Lester 我们还是警察吗
Lester, are we still cops?
- 技术上来说 我想是的 - 好的 我只是核实下
- Technically, I suppose so. - Okay, I was just checking.
Keisha不接电话 她也不在家
Keisha ain't called, and she ain't been home.
你离开时她好吗
How was she when you left her?
告诉过你 她病了
She was sick, I told you that.
她昨晚没来上班 今天也没去领工资
She missed work last night and she ain't been down there to pick up her check today.
你知道吗
You know something?
这个游戏
This game...
我舅舅的生意...
This thing with my uncle...
我在想 可能不适合我
Might not be right for me, I'm thinking.
你为什么这么说
Why do you say that?
除了钱没啥好处
Nothing good to it but the money.
听上去和我的工作很像
Sounds a lot like my job.
我是说 你让人们相互利用
I mean, you got people using each other.
相互欺骗
Scamming each other.
付钱晚了就给人大卸八块
Cutting each other up because they're late on a bill.
开枪打人 就因为他口袋里他妈的可能有一块钱
Shooting folks because there might be a fucking dollar in it.
有时候 我他妈的都喘不过气来
It gets to sometime like I can't even fucking breathe.
好像我都无法呼吸了
Like I can't even get no air.
你懂我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
干点别的呗
Do something else.
那么 你对自己的工作满意吗
So, you happy with your job?
妈的
Shit.
那么 干点别的呗
Well then, do something else.
有啊 以后也不得不 妈的
I am. I'm going to have to. Shit.
哪能永远都漂亮
Can't stay pretty forever.
没有永远 是吧 Dee?
It's not forever, right, Dee?
然后呢
And then what?
你现在就很美
You pretty now.
我们现在很美
Now we pretty.
接到了 我会打回来的
You got me, holler back.
Dee 哥们
Dee, man.
起床 快过来 Stink被干了 哥们
Raise up and roll in quick. Stink been got, man.
你听到了吗  他们干了Stink
You hear me? They got Stink.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
谁接了昨晚Edmondson街的案子 Anton Artis的那个
Who caught the one from Edmondson last night? Anton Artis.
Cole 和Dunnigan那的人的协助
Cole, with an assist from Dunnigan.
Omar是那个开枪的人
Omar was the shooter.
我操
Fuck me.
都在监听的录音里
It's all over the wiretap.
好吧 我们理理思路
Okay, let's see.
我们以一个目击证人的证词 搞定一个谋杀案
We put down one murder on the testimony of one eyewitness...
而这个目击证人后来又去做了另一个人
Who then goes out and drops somebody else.
嗯 是给他的男朋友Brandon报仇
Yeah, it was payback for his boyfriend, Brandon.
Anton Artis就是Stinkum 抓走Brandon并做了他的人之一
Anton Artis is Stinkum, one of the boys who snatched Brandon and did him up.
我相信那个操蛋的有他的理由 Jimmy...
I'm sure that motherfucker had his reasons, Jimmy--
你想放弃Gant案 那就告诉Cole开枪人的名字
You want to give back the Gant case, then tell Cole the name of his shooter.
否则 就告诉他我们在窃听时听到风声了
Otherwise, tell him we're hearing talk on the wire...
我们结案后就会帮他破案
And we'll give him his clearance once we wrap our case.
但你不会
But you won't.
不 我们不会
No, we won't.
你要我过去 为你骗Cole不要管这个案子?
You want me to go and bullshit Cole out of his case for you?
- 你干嘛自己不和他说呢 - 你在开玩笑吗
- Why don't you go tell him yourself? - Are you kidding?
如果Rawls看到我有插过手 他还不宰了我
If Rawls sees my fingerprints on this, he'll run my nuts through a cheese grater.
去你的 Jimmy
Fuck you, Jimmy.
- 工作还顺利吗 - 挺顺利的
- How's it going with it? - Pretty good.
我喜欢这个和受害者前女友有一腿的伙子
I like this kid who's fucking my victim's old girlfriend.
Ray 我能和你说一会儿话吗
Ray, can I talk to you for a minute?
去我办公室
In my office.
面对这样的案子 你会置身于一种古怪的境地
With cases like this one, you are put in some strange fucking places.
Cole今年干得不错 他不需要破这件案子
Cole's doing good this year, he don't need the clearance.
好吧 我知道这会把他骗惨了
All right, I know this fucks him.
我告诉他 你将来会把开枪人交给他时 他的那个表情 你真该看看
You should've seen his face when I told him you'd give him his shooter down the road.
他很开心?
He's happy?
嗯 他看着我就像只该死的小狗崽
Yeah. He looked at me like a damn puppy.
对不起 Bunk
I'm sorry, Bunk.
我扛得住
I'll carry it.
去他妈的
Fuck it.
不 今晚我请
No, tonight's mine.
听着 告诉你 我撤了
Look, I'll tell you what, I'm going to roll out.
这些钱算我请你
Here's the money I would've spent on your ass.
Jimmy
Jimmy.
打电话给Nadine告诉她我加班 上街出任务
Call Nadine and tell her I caught one, and I'm out on the street.
我为你说了谎 不是吗
I lied for you, didn't l?
你有空吗
You got a minute?
嗯 什么事
Yeah, what's up?
我想我可能搞砸了
I think I might have fucked something up.
是吗
Yeah?
几星期前 我和Omar谈
I'm interviewing Omar, a few weeks back.
他告诉我Bird是Gant案中的开枪者
And he's giving it to me that Bird is the shooter in the Gant case.
他告诉我如果我们如果我们抓到Bird 他身上会有那把枪
He tells me, if we catch up to Bird, he'll have the gun on him.
的确如此啊
Which he does.
糟糕的是我告诉他我们需要一个目击证人
But the thing is I told him that we needed an eyeball witness.
那时 他自告奋勇
At which point, he volunteers.
也许他看见了
Maybe he saw it.
也许他掺和进来只是想看Bird被关起来
Or maybe he put himself in it just to see Bird locked up.
我的印象里他们相互之间可没什么好感
I got the impression there wasn't much love between them.
我搞砸了 是吧?
I fucked up, didn't l?
有一点
A little.
但枪是匹配的
But the gun matches.
在描绘和叙述上他也和我们的证人一致
And he's consistent with our witness on the description and the scenario.
所以 别担忧
So, don't sweat it.
Kima
Kima.
讯问更像是门艺术 而不是科学
You know, interrogation is more art than science.
大多数时候你得靠直觉来干
You've got to feel your way through on instinct, mostly.
来 看看这个
Come, take a look at this.
她们是谁
Who are they?
Barksdale俱乐部里上班的一些舞女
Some dancers who work at Barksdale's club.
我从酒类控制局的投诉和州雇员档案里
I pulled their names off of liquor board complaints...
找到她们的资料
And state employment records.
如果你要试着讯问其中的一个 你会挑哪个?
If you were going to try to turn one these girls, which one would it be?
她
Her.
为什么
Why?
首先 她没有犯罪记录
She doesn't have a record, for one thing.
只有一张驾照的照片
She's just a DMV photo.
还有呢
Why else?
我不知道 我说不出来
I don't know. I can't really say.
我喜欢她的脸
I like her face.
灵魂 良心 随便你怎么叫 她是个良民 对吧
Soul, conscience, whatever you want to call it. She's a citizen, right?
从眼睛里能看出来
It's in the eyes.
直觉 警探
Instinct, Detective.
喂
Yeah?
啥
What?
你是谁
Who is this?
真的吗
He did?
你怎么知道我的号码
How the hell did you get my number?
嗯 好的
Yeah, okay.
嗯
Yeah.
女士?
Ma'am?
把这个疯疯癫癫的混蛋弄走
Get this crazy bastard out of here.
怎么了
What's the matter?
他两次弄响了失火警报器
He set off the smoke alarm, twice.
不赖吧
That good?
在浴室里
In the bathroom.
Bunk 我是Jimmy
Bunk, it's Jimmy.
搞什么
What the fuck?
Bunk 它妈的快醒醒
Bunk, wake the fuck up.
- Bunk 醒醒 - 咋了
- Bunk, wake up. - What?
- 你它妈的搞什么 - 我听到了Jimmy
- The fuck are you doing? - I hear you, Jimmy.
你在干什么 你他妈的衣服呢
What are you doing? Where are your fucking clothes?
这儿
Right here.
谁在乎啊
Who gives a shit?
- 得了吧 哥们 - 不要
- Come on, man. - No.
干嘛烧衣服啊 哥们?
What did you burn your clothes for, man?
上面有头发 有纤维
Got hair, got fibers and...
有骚味...
Got pussy on it and....
啥 微量物证?
What, trace evidence?
你闻到骚味了吗?
You smell pussy?
我已经闻不到骚味了
I don't smell no pussy no more.
你少来
Knock it off.
我想你可以送我回去了
I think you all can just take my ass home.
痕迹科找不出Bunk的什么把柄
Trace lab ain't going to have shit on the Bunk.
那鸟玩意儿 没有它妈的案子可立 警探
That shit. No fucking case file, Detective.
你它妈的鞋子呢 哥们?
Where are your fucking shoes, man?
女士 你看到过他的鞋子吗
Ma'am, you seen his shoes?
给我惹了一身骚 现在还要拿走我的鞋?
Give me that pussy, and now you going to take my shoes?
这可不对 妈的
That ain't right, shit.
妈的
Shit.
老天 Jimmy
Christ, Jimmy.
Bunk 我说烧毁证据合情合理
Bunk, I'll give you that burning trace evidence makes sense.
可你它妈的准备穿什么回去
What the fuck did you plan to wear home?
妈的
Shit.
Jimmy 你知道吗
Jimmy, you know something?
你真是颗煞星 哥们
You're no good for people, man.
我是说 该死
I mean, damn.
你周围的所有人...
Everybody around you....
老天
Christ.